

Boston, MA

📳 (+1) 978-201-5748 | 💌 robbenzmann@gmail.com | 😭 robbmann.io | 🖸 renzmann | 🛅 renzmann

# **Summary** \_

Sr. Data Scientist with a track record of empowering data science teams to build robust software and run faster as a result. I specialize in the gap between business analytics and software engineering to help both teams deliver more value together.

# Work Experience \_

#### **CVS Health - Analytics & Behavior Change**

Welleslev, MA

SR. DATA SCIENTIST

Aug. 2022 - Present

- Implemented a BigQuery dataset with machine learning features supporting over \$100 MM of revenue through targeted member-level marketing materials and plan sponsor acquisition & retention.
- Led technical design and implementation of a retrieval-assisted generative chat web application that indexed hundreds of unstructured documents (word, ppt, pdf) and assisted sales representatives in accurately presenting and selling Aetna's products to its 14.5 million commercial
- · Wrote and instructed an interactive "Let's Git Going" course for internal use that brought 50+ developers to a professional level using the Git version control system.

### **N1 Health (formerly Algorex Health Technologies)**

Boston, MA

SR. DATA SCIENTIST

Mar. 2021 - Aug. 2022

- · Principal developer of the internal Python software development kit, reducing the environment setup time from 45 minutes to 30 seconds and increasing net-new developer throughput by 50%.
- · Implemented automatic scaling and shutdown for data science architecture, saving \$40,000 annually and reducing on-boarding time from 3 days to 15 minutes.
- Led modeling of COVID-19 vaccine adoption rates for 3,500 vulnerable members around the greater Boston area, leading to targeted outreach recommendations.

antuit.ai Frisco, TX

DATA SCIENTIST (PRICING AND MARKETING)

Sep. 2017 - Mar. 2021

- · Wrote an optimization algorithm for strategic pricing of consumer healthcare products in 11 countries, modeling more than \$5Bn in revenue across 8 product categories per country.
- · Created ETL pipelines that prepared 1+ TB consumer healthcare product sales for a data warehouse. I also designed over 50 custom views in the warehouse that reduced the average data scientist query time from 5 minutes to a few seconds and reduced the team's query costs by 80 percent.
- · Modeled customer churn and lifetime value for over 1 MM members for an international medical cosmetics provider.

## Core Skills\_

#### **Tools & Languages**

I DABBLE IN MANY OTHERS - BUT THESE ARE MY BREAD & BUTTER

- Python and all its messy history of packaging systems pip, conda, poetry, pipeny, ...
- · GNU/Unix: Git, Bash, Make, SSH
- · SQL: Google BigQuery, AWS Athena, PostgreSQL, SQLite
- · Enough HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Go, Markdown, LaTeX, and Org to get my personal website and this resume up and running.

#### **Tech Stack**

WHERE AND HOW I'VE DEPLOYED THINGS

- · Azure, AWS, Google Cloud Platform
- Databricks, SageMaker, Docker, Terraform, Jenkins
- Jekyll, GitHub pages, and GitHub actions for my personal website.

## Education

## **Miami University** MASTER OF MATHEMATICS

Oxford, OH

Sep. 2011 - May 2017

• Master's topic: The Container Method for Triangle-induced Hypergraphs

- · 2017 Journal award

Miami University Oxford, OH

B.A. Music Sep. 2011 - May 2015

- 4-year music scholarship.
- Focus in music technology, recording, and audio acoustic design.